<?xml version="1.0"?>
<entry>
    <id>2</id>
    <title description="09/04 - 09/10">Week 2</title>
    <content>
        <row>
            <header>What did you do this past week?</header>
            <text>
                This past week, I've been doing a lot of reading form my literature class and do a lot of interview prep
                practice. I went on a hike on Saturday then spent the rest of the weekend working on Data Mining and
                SWE. Data Mining took me over 6-7 hours to complete, but now I don't have to worry about it during the
                week. I've spent about 5 hours working on SWE, and I couldn't get it. I feel like I should have taken a
                break and talk with a TA or something.
            </text>
        </row>
        <row>
            <header>What's in your way?</header>
            <text>
                SWE project took me a little bit by surprise. The problem was a little bit different from what I did for
                OOP. I've tried 2 different types of cache, but neither was fast enough for HackerRank. I'll try my last
                option tomorrow.
            </text>
        </row>
        <row>
            <header>What will you do next week?</header>
            <text>
                I have quite a few things to prepare for prior to the careers fair. I'd like to revamp my personal
                website and put it on a more professional domain. However, my first priority is still practicing my
                pitch and review companies' hiring positions.
            </text>
        </row>
        <row>
            <header>What's my experience of the class?</header>
            <text>
                I feel like Prof. Downing is less prepared for SWE than he was for OOP. That being said, the class
                overall is still very organized and well-structured compared to a lot of other CS classes I've taken.
            </text>
        </row>
        <row>
            <header>What's my pick-of-the-week or tip-of-the-week?</header>
            <text>
                I would recommend who doesn't know about Jupyter iPython Notebook to check it out. It has helped me work
                so much quicker on the project so far. Installing and setting it up are easy. Once done, you can have a
                quick and pretty interactive UI for running python. You can read more
                <link href="http://jupyter-notebook-beginner-guide.readthedocs.io/en/latest/what_is_jupyter.html"> here.</link>
            </text>
        </row>

    </content>
</entry>