<?xml version="1.0"?>
<entry>
    <title description="09/11 - 09/17">Week 3</title>
    <content>
        <row>
            <header>What did you do this past week?</header>
            <text>
                This past week, I finished a bunch of projects for my classes. I spent some time 2 days before career
                fair to prepare an elevator pitch. It was really helpful at the FoCS brunch and career fair. Nobody has
                ever told me to prepare an elevator pitch for career fairs like this. However, I've started recommending
                my friends to do this. I'll write more in detailed below. At career fair, I talked to about 10-15
                companies. I mostly picked companies that have offices in Austin, since I want to stay here after
                graduation. Moreover, those local companies are the ones that I usually have more engaging conversations
                with. I skipped Amazon, Microsoft, Google and all other big Silicone Valley companies. Why? They will
                tell you to apply online, and the lines are very long, which take up your valuable time that you can use
                to talk to other cool smaller tech companies.
            </text>
        </row>
        <row>
            <header>What's in your way?</header>
            <text>
                I have some Algorithm homework that I need to finish by Wednesday. It's starting to pick up pace very
                quickly. I hope I will not be overwhelmed by all the work during this semester
            </text>
        </row>
        <row>
            <header>What will you do next week?</header>
            <text>
                I have to apply for FT positions online for some of the companies that I talked to at the career fair. A
                lot of readings for algorithm and literature class need to be done, but I don't know how many I'll get
                to do.
            </text>
        </row>
        <row>
            <header>What's my experience of the class?</header>
            <text>
                Like last week, I think the class is a bit less structured than OOP (C++). I'm looking forward to the
                group projects though, because that's what I want to get out of the class. I think that the class will
                help me getting started with Python professionally.
            </text>
        </row>
        <row>
            <header>What's my pick-of-the-week or tip-of-the-week?</header>
            <text>
                Now, let's talk about elevator pitch. I recommend every single college student to make an elevator pitch
                that sells yourself to an employer. You start out with your name, then tell them about what you're
                interested in or something that you're passionate about. If you don't have a particular interest in any
                field, says that! Do not lie! Then, tell them about your experience and background. End the pitch with
                what you are looking for (internship, FT positions, etc.) Sometime, you might start with what you are
                looking for first, since they might not have that opportunity currently. So, you don't have to waste
                time talking to them and move on to the next company. Again, elevator pitch can be used in many
                different situations, so just make sure you streamline it to fit the purpose of the event.
            </text>
        </row>

    </content>
</entry>