<?xml version="1.0"?>
<entry>
    <id>4</id>
    <title description="09/18 - 09/24">Week 4</title>
    <content>
        <row>
            <header>What did you do this past week?</header>
            <text>
                This past week, I didn't do a lot. I spent a lot of time playing video games. However, I was able to
                close out on the regression testing for a project at work. It took me over a week to finish thoroughly
                with regression testing. Other than that, I just completed all other homeworks and finished several
                HackerRank coding challenges that were sent to me.
            </text>
        </row>
        <row>
            <header>What's in your way?</header>
            <text>
                Midterm season is coming. I have an exam this Thursday for my literature class. I'm not fully prepared
                for that exam, so I will be spending a lot of my time during the week on this. Additionally, I have all
                projects/homework for other class due sometime during this week as well.
            </text>
        </row>
        <row>
            <header>What will you do next week?</header>
            <text>
                Other than having all the homeworks and projects due this week, I only have to plan on picking up my
                friend from the airport on Friday. It will be my busiest week of the semester yet.
            </text>
        </row>
        <row>
            <header>What's my experience of the class?</header>
            <text>
                It's still going quite slow. I'm sure that it is only because I've taken OOP with Downing before.
                However, I'm super excited for the group project. I will be working on the backend and database mostly.
                I haven't started much, and I should.
            </text>
        </row>
        <row>
            <header>What's my pick-of-the-week or tip-of-the-week?</header>
            <text>
                My pick of the week is Memo.ai. It is a slack intergration that allows you and your team to take notes
                more effectively. It also allows you to document your meetings, project plans, work progress much more
                effectively. You can try it out for free for 14 days, then $10 per month for first 5 users. Check them
                out here:<link href="http://www.memo.ai"> Memo.ai</link>
            </text>
        </row>

    </content>
</entry>