<?xml version="1.0"?>
<entry>
    <title description="10/02 - 10/08">Week 6</title>
    <content>
        <row>
            <header>What did you do this past week?</header>
            <text>
                This past week, I don't have a lot of due assignments other than 2 midterms in algorithms and data
                mining. I think did fairly well on both of them, so I'm hoping to get decent grades back. Other than
                that, I spent a lot of time closing out my current project at work. I've also started on the database
                for my project. After talking to Prof Downing about costly CloudSQL pricing plans, he suggested me
                hosting it on a VM. I did that successfully, but I don't know what the workload will be for the always
                free tier of compute engine. However, I'm sure that it's good enough for a development database so we do
                not get charged every month.
            </text>
        </row>
        <row>
            <header>What's in your way?</header>
            <text>
                I hate to say it, but ACL is coming up for me next weekend. Although I'm not worrying about ACL itself,
                I need to give the works that will be due the week right after ACL. I doubt that I would work over the
                weekend while going to ACL at the same time.
            </text>
        </row>
        <row>
            <header>What will you do next week?</header>
            <text>
                I'm going to spend 1-2 days studying for SWE midterm and making a cheat sheet. After that, I will have
                to start making notes and anaylsis for a literature paper that will be due after Halloween weekend. Next
                Algorithm homework will also be out, so I'll be working on that.
            </text>
        </row>
        <row>
            <header>What's my experience of the class?</header>
            <text>
                We spent a lecture day for our TA to introduce us to ReactJS and how we will be using it for our
                project. It was really helpful to get us started. ReactJS seems definitely hard to work with at first,
                but I've walked through the tutorial and I can see how it helps smooth the website development process a
                lot.
            </text>
        </row>
        <row>
            <header>What's my pick-of-the-week or tip-of-the-week?</header>
            <text>
                My pick-of-the-week is Todoist. It's a todo list application that has both wonderful UI and
                well-integrated functions. If you're a developer, you would start thinking of your daily, weekly,
                monthly or even long-term tasks as either some tickets or projects. Then for each task, you can break
                them down into smaller tasks, assign due date, categories, etc. What I like most about Todoist is its
                ability to schedule your tasks on a reoccurrence basis (weekly, monthly, every 10th day, etc.). Also,
                the software is well-integrated across many platforms (Android, Windows, Mac, iOS, etc.)
            </text>
        </row>
    </content>
</entry>