<?xml version="1.0"?>
<entry>
    <id>7</id>
    <title description="10/09 - 10/15">Week 7</title>
    <content>
        <row>
            <header>What did you do this past week?</header>
            <text>
                This past week, I discovered some new hidden works to be done for my project at work, so the project is
                going to take quite a bit longer than expected. Other than that, I've spent a lot of time studying for
                SWE exam on Thursday. I think that I did fairly well, just not as well as I hoped for. However, I'll be
                sure to stay on top of my quizzes and projects to make up for that points lost. I also went to ACL over
                the weekend. It was quite an experience for me.
            </text>
        </row>
        <row>
            <header>What's in your way?</header>
            <text>
                Some assignments are given out for all my classes already. I really need to push myself to get started
                on those because it will all be due on the weekend of Halloween, which I will be out of town.
            </text>
        </row>
        <row>
            <header>What will you do next week?</header>
            <text>
                This coming week, I will be doing a lot of homework for this and the week after as well. I have another
                music festival to go to during Halloween weekend, so I need to get myself ready for it and not lack
                behind academically.
            </text>
        </row>
        <row>
            <header>What's my experience of the class?</header>
            <text>
                The way Prof Downing went over the difference in between */** in function definition and function call
                really was helpful to me. It gave me a basic understanding of the difference functionalities of these
                two symbols in two different context. I tried to read further about it through python documentation, and
                I realized that there are a lot more details and precautions. I really enjoyed lectures this past week.
            </text>
        </row>
        <row>
            <header>What's my pick-of-the-week or tip-of-the-week?</header>
            <text>
                My pick-of-the-week is Gitlab. As an open-source project, GitLab provides many powerful development
                tools like version control or Agile board, all with beautiful and user-friendly interface. You guys
                should check it out!
            </text>
        </row>
    </content>
</entry>