<?xml version="1.0"?>
<entry>
    <id>8</id>
    <title description="10/16 - 10/22">Week 8</title>
    <content>
        <row>
            <header>What did you do this past week?</header>
            <text>
                This past week, I finished a lot of works for my classes early. I got my HackerRank grades back for SWE
                exam, and I did well. I'm happy with it. I also started to make my personal website at
                <link href="http://www.thienmint.com"> www.thienmint.com</link>
                . It is not finished, but I will start porting my blog over there soon. I'm using
                Python and Flask to play more with the Jinja2 templating system. It's very neat. I got the website up
                and running within just an hour.
            </text>
        </row>
        <row>
            <header>What's in your way?</header>
            <text>
                Some assignments are due this coming week. I've started on all of it. I just need to not procrastinate
                and continue working on it until I'm finished. Other than that, I don't have much else to do for school,
                and I'm going to start on a new project at work.
            </text>
        </row>
        <row>
            <header>What will you do next week?</header>
            <text>
                This coming week, I will be doing a lot of homework for this and the week after as well. I have another
                music festival to go to next weekend, so I need to get myself ready for it and not lack behind
                academically. I will also suggest to my boss and mentor that I should start working on a new project
                concurrently with testing the already existing project.
            </text>
        </row>
        <row>
            <header>What's my experience of the class?</header>
            <text>
                I find this week's lectures on SQL stuff a little bit silly. I guess it wasn't very helpful for me
                because I have done this kind of querying data from databases before. However, it was interesting to see
                how */** in function defintion and function call applied here.
            </text>
        </row>
        <row>
            <header>What's my pick-of-the-week or tip-of-the-week?</header>
            <text>
                My pick-of-the-week is Dashlane. It s a password manager software that allows you to keep track of your
                password in a secure environment. It automatically enable 2-factor authorization for unknown machines.
                It also assess your password. It will tell you how weak your passwords are and the reasons why. It can
                also automatically change your password for many many website, like Amazon. The free version is great if
                you only want to use it on 1 machine, but the premium version is great for syncing across mutliple
                devices. You should check it out!
            </text>
        </row>
    </content>
</entry>