<?xml version="1.0"?>
<entry>
    <id>9</id>
    <title description="10/23 - 10/29">Week 9</title>
    <content>
        <row>
            <header>What did you do this past week?</header>
            <text>
                This past week, I worked a lot on the SWE project. Since we are hosting our on MySQL on the Google Cloud
                Compute Engine, I have to make sure that it is up and running manually. It gives me a good experience to
                host and work with a database. I wrote some Bash script that check for the database's upstate and
                restart if necessary. Also, I installed a swapfile so that we can deal with the lowest amount of RAM
                that avialable for always-free tier, which is 600 MB.
            </text>
        </row>
        <row>
            <header>What's in your way?</header>
            <text>
                I have data mining exam on Tuesday. Then, I have my sprint review at work. For this sprint review, I
                will need to show the progress I've made on my new and last project at MaxPoint.
            </text>
        </row>
        <row>
            <header>What will you do next week?</header>
            <text>
                This coming week, on Monday, I will be studying for my Data Mining exam that is on Tuesday. I will be do
                critical reading for some literary works for my English class, so that I can write an essay on them for
                the upcoming week.
            </text>
        </row>
        <row>
            <header>What's my experience of the class?</header>
            <text>
                Since I've already been doing MySQL and database for the entire project's duration, the technical SQL
                stuffs from lectures were not new to me. I appreciate Prof. Downing explaining all different kinds of
                joins a lot, because it seems like a lot of people still can't distinguish each from another.
            </text>
        </row>
        <row>
            <header>What's my pick-of-the-week or tip-of-the-week?</header>
            <text>
                My pick-of-the-week is Trello API. It allows you to query down the information for the boards that you
                have access to. This way, I will be able to make a simple web UI that will dynamically generate
                information that I am interested to see. For example, I want to see unfinished tickets assigned to each
                person and their progress all in a simple UI. I'm planning on developing something that I can customize
                for my team.
            </text>
        </row>
    </content>
</entry>