<?xml version="1.0"?>
<entry>
    <id>10</id>
    <title description="10/30 - 11/05">Week 10</title>
    <content>
        <row>
            <header>What did you do this past week?</header>
            <text>
                This past week, I spent a lot of time studying for my Data Mining class and writing essay for my
                literature class. I think I did fairly well on the Data Mining. Other than that, I spent some time
                working problems on LeetCode to prepare myself for future technical interviews. I realize that your
                technical background for an entry-level position isn't always required to be fantastic. They know you
                won't have Senior level experience coming out of college. So, it all falls down to the interview a lot
                of time.
            </text>
        </row>
        <row>
            <header>What's in your way?</header>
            <text>
                I have data mining exam on Tuesday. Then, I have my sprint review at work. For this sprint review, I
                will need to show the progress I've made on my new and last project at MaxPoint.
            </text>
        </row>
        <row>
            <header>What will you do next week?</header>
            <text>
                This coming week, I will be working on SWE a lot. I will have to find a way to automatically deploy our
                dev version of the website to compute engine instead of Flexible App Engine. Flexible App Engine is just
                way too expensive to run our frontend. At the minimalist configuration, it still costs us about $1.50 a
                day. Yes, the educational fund will last us through the semester, but I would like to keep the site up
                and running for as long as possible.
            </text>
        </row>
        <row>
            <header>What's my experience of the class?</header>
            <text>
                The Regex lecture was very refreshing. I have been using regex a lot to convert repetitive Java code
                into Scala. I didn't realize that a lot of people in class do not have the same kind of Regex
                experience, so the lecture definitely was useful in introducing regex to everyone who hasn't worked with
                it.
            </text>
        </row>
        <row>
            <header>What's my pick-of-the-week or tip-of-the-week?</header>
            <text>
                My pick-of-the-week is this video below. I've been around a lot of cats recently, and I have never seen
                a cat who never jump to their food when given. It's just nice to sympathize with this mother cat.
                <link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cH8Wya0WiuE"> Watch here!</link>
            </text>
        </row>
    </content>
</entry>