<?xml version="1.0"?>
<entry>
    <id>11</id>
    <title description="11/06 - 11/12">Week 11</title>
    <content>
        <row>
            <header>What did you do this past week?</header>
            <text>
                This past week, I spent most of my time working on SWE project after taking my algorithm exam and
                turning my essay for my literature class. Other members in my group were very busy with other classes
                like compute graphics or visualization, so although I don't know a lot about ReactJS, I injected myself
                into the frontend side of the project to help them out. We submitted everything about 1 minute away from
                the deadline, so I don't know what it would be like if I hadn't helped implementing the filtering and
                sorting.
            </text>
        </row>
        <row>
            <header>What's in your way?</header>
            <text>
                It is my last week at my internship, I will be pressured a little bit to finish everything up and hand
                off the projects to other teams. Other than that, I will just have final exams lurking up very soon.
                Also, I will ensure that all my team members start on the last phase of the project because I don't want
                to be the one to spend 12-20 hours over 2 days working on all aspects of it.
            </text>
        </row>
        <row>
            <header>What will you do next week?</header>
            <text>
                I don't have a lot of things due for this coming week. However, this is the perfect time for me to start
                preparing for my final exams for my other classes, so I will be doing that. I will also need to start
                planning for my vacation plan for winter break. I'm just so excited for the coming break!
            </text>
        </row>
        <row>
            <header>What's my experience of the class?</header>
            <text>
                SQL stuff are really fun for me. I think the way Prof. Downing teach SQL is interesting. He purposely
                shows the intuitive way to write SQL queries but wrong first. This way, he effectively introduces both
                the right and wrong way to do things and the specific reasons why.
            </text>
        </row>
        <row>
            <header>What's my pick-of-the-week or tip-of-the-week?</header>
            <text>
                My pick-of-the-week an app called Forest.It is pretty much the gamification of a productivity app. You
                play the game by growing trees. However, unlike a typical game, when you're growing your tree, you can't
                use your phone at all or it will die. It's supposed to motivate you to stay off your phone after you've
                set out a certain block of time commitment to focus on some task. You can choose from 15 - 120 minutes
                duration. It's completely free, and if you buy the premium version, you get to label your focus block of
                time and ability to unlock more different types of tree.
            </text>
        </row>
    </content>
</entry>