<?xml version="1.0"?>
<entry>
    <title description="11/13 - 11/19">Week 12</title>
    <content>
        <row>
            <header>What did you do this past week?</header>
            <text>
                This past week, I spent a lot of time at work investigating an size inflation issues on the data that is
                newly produced by our new preferable technologies stack (Scala/Spark instead of Java/Cascading).
                Surprisingly enough, it had to do with the ordering of data before it is being fed to a compressor. We
                still don't know how Cascading figured out the optimal ordering of data or how Spark's shuffling of data
                affecting the compression effectiveness. Although I haven't been able to resolve these issues before I
                left for good on Friday, my mentor told me that my finding could help save a lot of money for the
                company because they can go bac to old gigantic data sets that are just taking up a lot of space and
                reduce the size. Even a small fraction reduction could mean thousands, if not hundred of thousands, of
                dollars.
            </text>
        </row>
        <row>
            <header>What's in your way?</header>
            <text>
                Since I've been working on my internship mostly over the past week, I still have a lot of homework and
                projects for school to start on. Specifically, I will have to refactor my backend code for SWE and help
                my frontend person to refactor a lot of the frontend code as well.
            </text>
        </row>
        <row>
            <header>What will you do next week?</header>
            <text>
                For SWE, I will be refactoring code and figure out a meaningful visualization of another group's data.
                For algorithm class, I will have to finish the NP-Complete homework before taking off for the break. For
                data mining, I might consider starting on it early, but if I end up not starting on the last project, I
                will still have 2 full weeks to do it after Thanksgiving.
            </text>
        </row>
        <row>
            <header>What's my experience of the class?</header>
            <text>
                This is where what I learned in OOP repeat in SWE. It's quite interesting to know a lot of the material
                already with inheritance and polymorphism from OOP, and as Prof Downing go over in SWE, I was able to
                refine my understanding of the subject.
            </text>
        </row>
        <row>
            <header>What's my pick-of-the-week or tip-of-the-week?</header>
            <text>
                My pick-of-the-week is an app called Automate on Android. This app allow you to make smart pipeline of
                phone actions. For example, when leaving my house's wifi network range, my phone will disable wifi
                automatically to save battery and prevent my phone from connecting to random public networks. Whenever
                I'm within range of UT campus, it will automatically enable wifi and attempts to connect to UTexas
                network. There are a lot more that you can do with it!
            </text>
        </row>
    </content>
</entry>